A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Minority Lawyers, 84-438, 1984-1985 (Reel 95, Frame 581)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Land Stewardship Project, 84-445, 1984-1987 (Reel 95, Frame 599)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Gifted Math, 85-511, 1985-1986 (Reel 95, Frame 623)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, 85-534, 1985-1986 (Reel 95, Frame 652)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Abstract, 85-556, 1985-1987 (Reel 95, Frame 670)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, International Studies, 86-610, 1986-1987 (Reel 95, Frame 699)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Gifted Math, 86-621, 1986-1987 (Reel 95, Frame 723)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Land Stewardship Project, 86-677, 1986-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 755)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, 86-683, 1986-1987 (Reel 95, Frame 789)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, International Center, 86-704, 1986-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 815)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Land Stewardship Project, 87-756, 1987-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 841)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, Minority Lawyers, 87-768, 1987-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 859)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, International Studies, 87-787, 1987-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 875)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, Minority Lawyers, 87-825, 1987-1988 (Reel 95, Frame 892)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Arkansas International Center, 87-847, 1987-1989 (Reel 95, Frame 906)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Land Stewardship Project, 88-27, 1988-1992 (Reel 95, Frame 927)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, 88-86, 1988-1989 (Reel 95, Frame 946)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, 88-87, 1988-1992 (Reel 95, Frame 960)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Reading Recovery, 90-35, Original Proposal-Year Two, 1990-1992 (Reel 95, Frame 1018)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Reading Recovery, 90-35, Year Three, 1992-1994 (Reel 96, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Children's Center, 92-162, 1992-1993 (Reel 96, Frame 210)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Break the Mold, 92-169, 1992-1994 (Reel 96, Frame 251)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Reading Recovery, 93-218, 1992-1995 (Reel 96, Frame 279)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, UALR 2000, 93-241, 1993-1996 (Reel 96, Frame 574)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Break the Mold, 93-246, Original Proposal, 1993-1998 (Reel 96, Frame 799)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Break the Mold, Grant Agreement-Year Three, 1993-1998 (Reel 96, Frame 1051)
      Grant number: 93-246
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Break the Mold, 93-246, Year Four-Year Five, 1995-1999 (Reel 97, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, KLRE/KUAR, 95-95, 1995-1998 (Reel 97, Frame 139)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Professional Services Agreement, 1995 (Reel 97, Frame 285)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, Department of Pediatrics, Low Birth Weight Infants, 79-1025, 1979-1982 (Reel 97, Frame 298)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, Little Rock Public Schools, Chronobiology Project, 79-1026, 1979-1982 (Reel 97, Frame 369)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, Nutrition Project, 80-138, 1980-1982 (Reel 97, Frame 441)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, Division of Medical Humanities, Medical Ethics Project, 82-259, 1982-1983 (Reel 97, Frame 536)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, 83-379, 1983-1984 (Reel 97, Frame 698)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, 84-451, 1984-1986 (Reel 97, Frame 721)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, 87-777, 1987-1989 (Reel 97, Frame 744)
    - University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, UAMS, Minority Student and Recruitment Retention, 88-168, 1988-1992 (Reel 97, Frame 762)
    - University of Arkansas at Monticello, UAM, 90-125, 1990-1992 (Reel 97, Frame 837)
    - University of Arkansas at Monticello, UAM, Break the Mold, 92-177, 1992-1993 (Reel 97, Frame 921)
    - University of Arkansas at Monticello, UAM, Break the Mold, 93-251, 1993-1994 (Reel 97, Frame 961)
    - University of Arkansas Monticello Foundation Fund, UAM, Acid Rain, 85-528, 1985-1987 (Reel 97, Frame 1058)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Wiley Branton Scholarship, 89-50, 1989 (Reel 97, Frame 1078)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Wiley Branton Scholarship, 89-118, 1989-1991 (Reel 97, Frame 1087)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Teachers of Tomorrow, 91-143, 1991-1993 (Reel 98, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Break the Mold, 92-170, 1992-1994 (Reel 98, Frame 146)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Minority Recruitment and Retention Project, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1992-1996 (Reel 98, Frame 170)
      Grant number: 92-194
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Minority Recruitment and Retention Project, 92-194, Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 98, Frame 345)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Minority Recruitment and Retention Project, 92-194, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1997 (Reel 98, Frame 576)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Break the Mold, 93-243, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1998 (Reel 98, Frame 864)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Break the Mold, 93-243, Year Two, 1994-1995 (Reel 99, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Break the Mold, 93-243, Year Three-Year Five, 1995-2000 (Reel 99, Frame 489)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, UABP/AM&N Alumni Association, Incorporated, 95-32, 1995-1996 (Reel 99, Frame 785)
    - University of Arkansas at Pine Bluff, UAPB, Professional Services Agreement, 1989-1990 (Reel 99, Frame 843)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Computer Controlled Courses, 83-332, 1983 (Reel 99, Frame 852)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, 83-380, 1983-1985 (Reel 99, Frame 871)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, 84-422, 1984-1986 (Reel 99, Frame 903)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, 84-454, 1984-1986 (Reel 99, Frame 949)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, 85-510, 1985-1986 (Reel 99, Frame 975)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Lead AR, 87-766, 1987-1988 (Reel 99, Frame 1008)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Lead AR, 88-57, 1988-1989 (Reel 99, Frame 1025)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Lead AR Program, 89-98, 1992-1998 (Reel 99, Frame 1047)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Leadership, 90-40, 1990-1991 (Reel 99, Frame 1114)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Leadership, 91-74, Original Proposal-Year One, 1991-1992 (Reel 100, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Leadership, 91-74, Year Two, 1992-1993 (Reel 100, Frame 257)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Middle Level Education, 92-85, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 100, Frame 430)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Middle Level Education, 92-85, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1997 (Reel 100, Frame 661)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, KUAF Public Affairs Division, 93-90, 1993-1996 (Reel 100, Frame 839)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, TCOC, Training Community Organizations for Change, 93-93, 1993-1994 (Reel 101, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, TCOC, Training Community Organizations for Change, 94-98, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1997 (Reel 101, Frame 352)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, TCOC, Training Community Organizations for Change, 94-98, Year Two-Year Three, 1995-1997 (Reel 101, Frame 644)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, TCOC, Training Community Organizations for Change, 94-98, Year Four-Year Five, 1997-1999 (Reel 101, Frame 879)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, Middle Level Education, 95-183, 1995-1996 (Reel 101, Frame 1085)
    - University of Arkansas Foundation System, 88-61, 1988-1992 (Reel 102, Frame 1)
    - University of Central Arkansas, Distance Education, 90-100, 1990-1993 (Reel 102, Frame 68)
    - University of Central Arkansas, Break the Mold, 92-178, 1992-1993 (Reel 102, Frame 135)
    - University of Central Arkansas, Break the Mold, 93-245, 1993-2000 (Reel 102, Frame 163)
    - University of Central Arkansas Foundation, Incorporated, 89-88, 1989-1990 (Reel 102, Frame 368)
    - University of North Carolina, 89-120, 1989-1990 (Reel 102, Frame 389)
    - Urban League of Arkansas, Incorporated, Research, 87-789, 1987-1988 (Reel 102, Frame 413)
    - Urban League of Greater Arkansas, Incorporated, Affordable Housing, 91-166, 1991-1995 (Reel 102, Frame 427)
    - Urban League of Greater Little Rock, Incorporated, GYST House, 78-1020, 1978-1979 (Reel 102, Frame 642)
    - Urban League of Greater Little Rock, Incorporated, 86-684, 1986-1988 (Reel 102, Frame 679)
    - Urban League of Greater Little Rock, Incorporated, Black Leadership, 87-765, 1987-1988 (Reel 102, Frame 722)
    - Valley Springs School District, Valley Springs Elementary School, 88-72, 1988-1989 (Reel 102, Frame 742)
    - Valley Springs School District, 92-14, 1992-1993 (Reel 102, Frame 762)
    - Valley Springs School District, 95-3, 1995 (Reel 102, Frame 804)
    - Van Buren Public Schools, 86-566, 1986 (Reel 102, Frame 836)
    - Venture Resources, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1992 (Reel 102, Frame 854)
    - Ventures in Education, 94-203, 1994-1997 (Reel 102, Frame 923)
    - Vilonia Public Schools, Vilonia Elementary School, 91-10, 1990-1991 (Reel 103, Frame 1)
    - Vilonia Public Schools, Vilonia Elementary School, 91-48, 1991 (Reel 103, Frame 71)
    - Vilonia Public Schools, 93-4, 1992-1993 (Reel 103, Frame 105)
    - Viola Public Schools, 89-15, 1989-1990 (Reel 103, Frame 130)
    - Violet Hill School District, 81-241, 1981-1982 (Reel 103, Frame 145)
    - Volunteers of America, Incorporated, 93-79, 1993-1995 (Reel 103, Frame 179)
    - Volunteers of America, Incorporated, 95-140, 1995-1996 (Reel 103, Frame 354)
    - Voter Education Project, Incorporated, 84-401, 1984-1985 (Reel 103, Frame 429)
    - Voter Education Project, Incorporated, 85-474, 1985-1987 (Reel 103, Frame 479)
    - Waldron Public Schools, 93-111, 1993-1994 (Reel 103, Frame 492)
    - Walnut Ridge School District, 85-543, 1985-1986 (Reel 103, Frame 544)
    - Warren Public Schools, 87-776, 1987-1988 (Reel 103, Frame 562)
    - Washington County Juvenile Court, 88-36, 1988-1990 (Reel 103, Frame 579)
    - Watershed Human and Community Development Agency, Incorporated, 89-72, 1989-1990 (Reel 103, Frame 614)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, Coleman Elementary School, 89-51, 1989-1990 (Reel 103, Frame 639)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, Edgewood Elementary School, 91-8, 1990-1991 (Reel 103, Frame 651)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, 91-89, 1991-1992 (Reel 103, Frame 699)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, Edgewood Elementary School, 92-57, 1992-1993 (Reel 103, Frame 734)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, Owen Elementary School, 92-121, 1992-1993 (Reel 103, Frame 776)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, 93-18, 1992-1993 (Reel 103, Frame 808)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, 95-154, 1995-1996 (Reel 103, Frame 858)
    - Watson Chapel Schools, 96-12, 1996 (Reel 103, Frame 899)
    - Weiner Public Schools, 89-104, 1989-1990 (Reel 103, Frame 939)
    - Weiner Public Schools, 92-58, 1992-1993 (Reel 103, Frame 961)
    - Weiner Public Schools, 93-163, 1993-1994 (Reel 103, Frame 1011)
    - Weiner Public Schools, School Improvement, 93-204, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1997 (Reel 104, Frame 1)
    - Weiner Public Schools, School Improvement, 93-204, Year Two-Year Five, 1995-2000 (Reel 104, Frame 212)
    - Weiner Public Schools, 95-130, 1995-1996 (Reel 104, Frame 357)
    - West, George, Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 104, Frame 401)
    - West Fork Public Schools, 85-524, 1985-1987 (Reel 104, Frame 410)
    - West Memphis School District, 95-18, 1995-1996 (Reel 104, Frame 430)
    - Western Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 85-501, 1985-1986 (Reel 104, Frame 482)
    - Western Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 86-619, 1986-1987 (Reel 104, Frame 513)
    - Western Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 88-124, 1988-1990 (Reel 104, Frame 536)
    - Western Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 89-28, 1989-1992 (Reel 104, Frame 553)
    - Western Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 95-103, 1995-1997 (Reel 104, Frame 619)
    - Western Yell County Schools, Western Yell Elementary School, 91-129, 1991-1992 (Reel 104, Frame 716)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, Westside Elementary School, 91-126, 1991-1992 (Reel 104, Frame 754)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 92-101, 1992-1993 (Reel 104, Frame 792)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 93-56, 1993-1994 (Reel 104, Frame 831)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 93-134, 1993-1994 (Reel 104, Frame 872)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 93-189, 1993-1994 (Reel 104, Frame 903)
    - Westside Consolidated School District, 95-114, 1995-1997 (Reel 104, Frame 931)
    - White County Central Schools, 92-112, 1992-1994 (Reel 104, Frame 959)
    - White County Central Schools, 93-17, 1993-1994 (Reel 104, Frame 991)
    - White Hall School District, 96-8, 1996 (Reel 104, Frame 1031)
    - Wilbur D. Mills Education Cooperative, 90-117, 1990-1991 (Reel 104, Frame 1066)
    - William Allen, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1982 (Reel 104, Frame 1100)
    - Williams Consulting, Professional Services Agreement, 1994-1995 (Reel 104, Frame 1106)
    - Williams, Dianne, Professional Services Agreement, 1988 (Reel 104, Frame 1135)
    - Wilowe Institute, 83-383, 1983-1985 (Reel 104, Frame 1140)
    - Wilowe Institute, 84-457, 1984-1987 (Reel 104, Frame 1168)
    - Wilowe Institute, 85-542, 1985-1987 (Reel 104, Frame 1191)
    - Wilowe Institute, 86-679, 1986-1988 (Reel 104, Frame 1221)
    - Wilowe Institute, 87-764, 1987-1988 (Reel 105, Frame 1)
    - Wilowe Institute, 88-84, 1988-1989 (Reel 105, Frame 20)
    - Wilowe Institute, 91-144, 1991-1994 (Reel 105, Frame 33)
    - Wilowe Institute, Professional Services Agreement, 1991 (Reel 105, Frame 132)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 85-540, 1985-1986 (Reel 105, Frame 139)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 86-695, 1986-1987 (Reel 105, Frame 178)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, 87-754, 1987-1989 (Reel 105, Frame 211)
    - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development, Professional Services Agreement, 1993 (Reel 105, Frame 234)
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Documentary on Arkansas Agriculture, 79-1027, 1978-1980 (Reel 105, Frame 266)
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Solar Energy Efficiency Project, 80-2041, 1980-1981 (Reel 105, Frame 333)
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Arkansas Central States Dairy Goat Marketing Cooperative, 80-2042, 1980-1984 (Reel 105, Frame 371)
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Arkansas Central States Dairy Goat Marketing Cooperative, 1980-1981 (Reel 105, Frame 399)
      Implementation Grant, 80-2043
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Family Farm Development Network, 81-257, 1981-1983 (Reel 105, Frame 472)
    - Winrock International Livestock Research and Training Center, Incorporated, Solar Energy Efficiency Project, 81-2041, 1981 (Reel 105, Frame 537)
    - Witts Springs School District, 88-12, 1988-1989 (Reel 105, Frame 581)
    - Wolfe-Kelly Community Development Council, Incorporated, 86-697, 1986-1988 (Reel 105, Frame 599)
    - Women's Educational Development Institute, 80-2045, 1980 (Reel 105, Frame 624)
    - Women's Project, Social Justice, 86-703, 1986-1987 (Reel 105, Frame 657)
    - Women's Project, 88-45, 1988-1991 (Reel 105, Frame 685)
    - The Woodstock Institute, Professional Services Agreement, 1985 (Reel 105, Frame 743)
    - Word Wrights, Professional Services Agreement, 1988 (Reel 105, Frame 749)
    - Wright, Clarence, Professional Services Agreement, 1991-1993 (Reel 105, Frame 760)
    - Wynne Public Schools, 93-168, 1993-1994 (Reel 105, Frame 818)
    - YARN, Incorporated, Youth Advocate and Resources Network, 92-69, 1992-1993 (Reel 105, Frame 866)
    - Yellville Summit Public Schools, Learning Partners, 87-772, 1987-1988 (Reel 105, Frame 938)
    - Yellville Summit Public Schools, 88-37, 1988 (Reel 105, Frame 959)
    - York-Hannover Case Study, Professional Services Agreement, 1984 (Reel 105, Frame 972)
    - YMCA of Metro Little Rock, Young Mens Christian Association, 93-91, 1993-1997 (Reel 106, Frame 1)
    - Youth Home, Incorporated, Arkansas Community Foundation, Mary F. McLeod Memorial Endowment, 77-1001, 1977-1978 (Reel 106, Frame 246)
    - Youth Home, Incorporated, 95-177, Original Proposal-Year One, 1995-1997 (Reel 106, Frame 275)
    - Youth Home, Incorporated, 95-177, Year Two-Year Three, 1997-1998 (Reel 106, Frame 431)
    - Unknown, (Morrison Associates), Youth Program Development, 78-1022, 1978-1979 (Reel 106, Frame 511)
    - Active Proposal File (Reel 106, Frame 566)
    - Correspondence, 1993-March 1994 (Reel 106, Frame 588)
    - Correspondence, 1994 April-June (Reel 106, Frame 701)
    - Correspondence, 1994 July-September (Reel 106, Frame 915)
    - Correspondence, 1994 October-December (Reel 107, Frame 1)
    - Correspondence, 1995 January-March (Reel 107, Frame 202)
    - Correspondence, 1995 April-June (Reel 107, Frame 309)
    - Correspondence, 1995 July-September (Reel 107, Frame 420)
    - Correspondence, 1995 October-December (Reel 107, Frame 636)
    - Correspondence, 1996 January-February (Reel 107, Frame 668)
    - Correspondence, 1996 March-April (Reel 107, Frame 890)
    - Correspondence, 1996 May-June (Reel 107, Frame 1050)
    - Correspondence, 1996 July-August (Reel 108, Frame 1)
    - Correspondence, 1996 September-October (Reel 108, Frame 206)
    - Correspondence, 1996 November-1997 February 1997 December (Reel 108, Frame 422)
    - Declination Letters, A-H, 1995-1996 (Reel 108, Frame 622)
    - Declination Letters, I-Y, 1996 (Reel 108, Frame 845)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1997 (Reel 109, Frame 1)
  - Discretionary Grants, 1977-1990; 2 (Reel 109, Frame 105)
    Small grants made by the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation.
    - Discretionary Grants, 1978 1977-1979 (Reel 109, Frame 106)
    - Discretionary Grants, 1979 1979 (Reel 109, Frame 163)
    - Discretionary Grants, 1980 1979-1982 (Reel 109, Frame 180)
    - Discretionary Grants, 1982 1982-1984 (Reel 109, Frame 415)
    - Discretionary Grants 1983, A-E, 1983-1984 (Reel 109, Frame 588)
    - Discretionary Grants 1983, H-Q, 1982-1984 (Reel 109, Frame 692)
    - Discretionary Grants 1983, S-Y, 1983-1985 (Reel 109, Frame 799)
    - Discretionary Grants 1984, A, 1984-1985 (Reel 109, Frame 965)
    - Discretionary Grants 1984, C-I, 1984-1985 (Reel 109, Frame 1126)
    - Discretionary Grants 1984, L-P, 1984-1985 (Reel 110, Frame 1)
    - Discretionary Grants 1984, S-W, 1984-1985 (Reel 110, Frame 130)
    - Discretionary Grants 1985, A, 1985-1986 (Reel 110, Frame 204)
    - Discretionary Grants 1985, C-L, 1985-1987 (Reel 110, Frame 301)
    - Discretionary Grants 1985, N-U, 1985-1987 (Reel 110, Frame 434)
    - Discretionary Grants 1986, A, 1986-1987 (Reel 110, Frame 554)
    - Discretionary Grants 1986, B-O, 1986-1987 (Reel 110, Frame 696)
    - Discretionary Grants 1986, P-U, 1986-1988 (Reel 110, Frame 852)
    - Discretionary Grants 1987, A-D, 1987-1988 (Reel 110, Frame 1015)
    - Discretionary Grants 1987, J-O, 1987-1988 (Reel 111, Frame 1)
    - Discretionary Grants 1987, P-W, 1987-1988 (Reel 111, Frame 84)
    - Discretionary Grants 1988, A-C, 1988-1989 (Reel 111, Frame 162)
    - Discretionary Grants 1988, E-O, 1988-1990 (Reel 111, Frame 292)
    - Discretionary Grants 1988, P-W, 1987-1990 (Reel 111, Frame 465)
    - Discretionary Grants 1989, A-D, 1989-1990 (Reel 111, Frame 623)
    - Discretionary Grants 1989, H-N, 1989-1990 (Reel 111, Frame 772)
    - Discretionary Grants 1989, P-U, 1989-1990 (Reel 111, Frame 928)
  - Education Mini-Grants, 1995-1998; 3 (Reel 111, Frame 1042)
    All the grants pertain to education.
    - Acorn School District, 97-4, 1997-1998 (Reel 111, Frame 1043)
    - Arkadelphia School District, 96-24, 1995-1996 (Reel 111, Frame 1076)
    - Atkins School District, 96-65, 1996-1997 (Reel 111, Frame 1105)
    - Beebe School District, 96-71, 1996-1998 (Reel 111, Frame 1147)
    - Benton School District, 96-54, 1996-1997 (Reel 111, Frame 1184)
    - Bentonville Public Schools, 96-144, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 1)
    - Blytheville Public Schools, 97-2, 1997-1998 (Reel 112, Frame 55)
    - Brinkley School District, 96-136, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 90)
    - Cave City School District, 96-10, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 125)
    - Conway Public Schools, 96-14, 1995-1996 (Reel 112, Frame 168)
    - Conway Public Schools, 96-18, 1995-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 208)
    - Conway Public Schools, 96-119, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 259)
    - Cotter School District, 97-16, 1997-1998 (Reel 112, Frame 296)
    - Danville Public Schools, 96-100, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 326)
    - Deer Consolidated Schools, 96-27, 1995-1996 (Reel 112, Frame 358)
    - Delta Special School District, 96-142, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 387)
    - El Dorado School District, 96-55, 1996 (Reel 112, Frame 423)
    - Elaine School District, 97-9, 1997-1998 (Reel 112, Frame 456)
    - Emerson School District, 97-14, 1996-1998 (Reel 112, Frame 482)
    - Farmington School District, 96-134, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 514)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 96-137, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 552)
    - Fayetteville Public Schools, 96-154, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 590)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 96-10, 1996 (Reel 112, Frame 642)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 96-22, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 669)
    - Fort Smith Public Schools, 97-12, 1997 (Reel 112, Frame 703)
    - Fountain Lake Public Schools, 96-102, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 731)
    - Genoa Central School District, 96-113, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 767)
    - Green Forest School District, 96-88, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 799)
    - Hamburg School District, 96-58, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 871)
    - Harrisburg School District, 96-138, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 913)
    - Harrison School District, 96-57, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 951)
    - Horatio School District, 96-53, 1996 (Reel 112, Frame 1003)
    - Jonesboro Public Schools, 96-19, 1995-1996 (Reel 112, Frame 1047)
    - Kirby School District, 96-139, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 1096)
    - Lake Hamilton School District, 96-77, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 1145)
    - Lakeside School District, 96-62, 1996-1997 (Reel 112, Frame 1217)
    - Lakeside School District, 96-111, 1996-1997 (Reel 113, Frame 1)
    - Leslie School District, 96-16, 1995-1996 (Reel 113, Frame 34)